## **Pham Van Toan**

(Front-end Developer)
Phone: 0903060651 / Email:phamvantoan1903@gmail.com
My website: tontonportfolio.netlify.app
Linkedln: www.linkedin.com/in/toanpham1903

#### **SUMMARY**

I have 2 years of experience in modern front-end web development and 9 months of data analyst

Since beginning my journey as a web developer, I've done many project related to education, stock, insurance, financial...

With my knowledge of UI/UX design, I enjoy solving front-end problems and creating the best user experience for users. I also spend time learning new technologies and best practices to become a better developer

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- 1. Programming Languages: Javascript & Typescript
- 2. Frameworks/Platforms:
  - ReactJS, VueJS, NextJS, NuxtJS
  - Redux, VueX
  - TailwindCss, AntD, MaterialUI, Boostrap, Sass
  - HTML, CSS
- 3. Database Management Systems: MS SQL Server, Oracle Database
- 4. Foreign Languages: TOEIC 565
- 5. Others:
  - Hands-on experience with RESTful APIs

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

**Rikkeisoft** - (Front-end Developer)

07/2022 - Now

**Project**: ProV AR (6 members) – 6 months

- **Description**: A web app is used to create a system to manage worker in construction site and help workers raise awareness of occupational safety. The system converts warnings from images into AR Manga animations to make workers more aware.
- Technologies: VueJS, Boostrap, VueX
- Responsibilities:
  - Analyzing business functions and coding assign screens (6 screens)
  - Giving estimation to the assign screens
  - Working with tester to complete screens

**Project**: NEC Fokuoka (3 members) – 5 months

- **Description**: A web app is used to manage information of residents in the city of Fukuoka
- Technologies: ReactJS, MaterialUI, ChartJS, Redux
- Responsibilities:
  - Fix bug and maintain UI

- Improve and update UI from feedback of client
- Optimize UI/UX system for system operate faster

## **Aegona** - (Front-end Developer)

05/2021 - 07/2022

**Project**: Smart Dragon Investment (2 members) – 4 months

- Description: A web app is platform to consult, support, provide information about stock investment
- Technologies: ReactJS, Redux, Highchart, TailwindCSS, AntD
- Responsibilities:
  - Analyzing business functions and coding all screens from design
  - Create core components UI
  - Research and apply highchart into project to show data chart
  - o Discuss and analyze API data returned to binding API suitably with client
  - Communicate with client and give a advices to optimize UI/UX

### **Project**: Engstar (4 members) – 5 months

• **Description**: A web app is used to manage questionaires, students and learn English online

### Technologies:

o Front-end: ReactJS, AntD, Redux

Back-end: Entity Framework, PostgresSQL

### Responsibilities:

- Analyzing business functions and coding screens from design
- Writing and designing RestfulAPI (just support)
- Discuss and analyze API data returned to binding API suitably with back-end developer
- Training and reviewing code of front-end member
- Maintain and update UI from feedback of client

#### **Project**: PTI Insurance Renewal Management (3 members) – 3 months

- **Description**: A web app is used to manage insurance contracts that are about to expire and assign it for employees to renew
- **Technologies**: ReactJS, AntD, Redux
- Responsibilities:
  - Analyzing business functions and coding screens from design
  - Discuss and analyze API data returned to binding API suitably with back-end developer
  - Giving estimation to the assign screens
  - Export excel report on demand
  - Fix bug and maintain UI/UX

# **Project**: Kitchen Visualization System 4'P (2 members) – 2 months

- **Description**: A web app is used to help chefs to manage the orders of dishes in sequence
- Technologies: ReactJS, AntD, Redux

### Responsibilities:

- o Analyzing business functions and coding all screens from design
- Discuss and analyze API data returned to binding API suitably with back-end developer
- o Communicate with client to discuss about business function and estimate it
- Fix bug and maintain UI/UX

#### **Biz4 Group** - (Data Analyst)

06/2020 - 03/2021

**Project**: MC Credit and FE Credit report (2 members)

• Technologies: MS SQL Server, Oracle Database

- Responsibilities:
  - o Export daily, monthly, quarterly report for client using stored procedure
  - Design data models from data warehouse, coding procedures and scripts for data migration
  - Optimize database system
  - Working with client to export report on demand

# **EDUCATION**

HCMC University of Food Industry (09/2016 – 09/2020)

Major: software technology

Degree grade: Good - GPA: 2.79